{
    "subject": "resource/Conquest_of_the_Planet_of_the_Apes",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/J._Lee_Thompson",
    "human_readable": "The director of Conquest of the Planet of the Apes is J. Lee Thompson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9110382795333862,
            "question": "Who directed Conquest of the Planet of the Apes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8005304932594299,
            "question": "Is J. Lee Thompson known for directing other films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7078045606613159,
            "question": "What other films has J. Lee Thompson directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6073973774909973,
            "question": "What is the name of the film Conquest of the Planet of the Apes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4964090585708618,
            "question": "What is the plot of Conquest of the Planet of the Apes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4960286319255829,
            "question": "Are there any sequels to Conquest of the Planet of the Apes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41645216941833496,
            "question": "What genre is Conquest of the Planet of the Apes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38375747203826904,
            "question": "When was Conquest of the Planet of the Apes released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3523343801498413,
            "question": "What are some common themes in J. Lee Thompson's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3334515690803528,
            "question": "How was Conquest of the Planet of the Apes received by critics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of Conquest of the Planet of the Apes is J. Lee Thompson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5440_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes in J. Lee Thompson's films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5440_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Conquest of the Planet of the Apes released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5440_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Conquest of the Planet of the Apes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5440_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5440_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5440_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5440_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5440_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5440_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5440_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5440_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5440_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5440_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5440_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Conquest of the Planet of the Apes\" was directed by J. Lee Thompson, which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}